all right hello and welcome to this
3-day interactive lab I'm excited that
you're here I wanted to load this up
with some pre-t trinings just to kind of
get the ball rolling on some of this I
know some of y'all you're at different
stages in your business whether you're
just trying to figure out where to start
trying to promote trying to get more
sales trying to figure out what
direction to take maybe your business
has been successful and you're
struggling now what I want to talk about
is this is why is AI so valuable why do
you need it can you do it without AI I
firmly believe today and whether you
agree with me or not that's honestly
doesn't matter to me uh I I've been
using AI for a couple years now before
anybody else had it I had access to it
if you look up when people actually
first got access to the AI engine known
as uh
gpt3
um chat GPT is the AI uh June 2020 was
the beta
version and and I had been using it
since uh right around January
2021 and so I've been using this AI
tools for 3 years uh most people have
only been using them for about a year at
this point that you're going to learn
from and so I learned very early
on that even before they had chat
GPT that if I communicate ated with the
AI um as if it was a person and asked it
questions um and and again this is what
people are saying like very early on it
was eerily good at writing amazingly
coherent text from
prompts were people were prompting it to
do things but if you actually asked it a
question it would be able to answer you
with an
answer and then
what what ended up happening was is that
the
model launched of chat GPT and then a
year ago almost a year ago exactly this
week uh GPT 4 came out and GPT 4 has
improved now a year later we have
multiple AI engines we have uh
grock what is grock grock
is uh Elon musk's
AI Elon Elon Musk helped found uh the
open AI
company and you know they have a they
have a whole article right here open Ai
and Elon
Musk and him founding it and all these
letters of when it was passed off and
anything things like that so you have
chat GPT you got
grock you have Gemini uh Advanced if you
look up Gemini Advanced and just what it
is and and and what it's capable of you
can get a trial of it right here uh the
1.0 Ultra model is really cool I guess
the 1.5 Ultra model is now available
I've never I've not used it but i' I've
heard that it's pretty
incredible um you have
cloud cloud like like
Claud Claude 3 Opus right here um I have
a I have a tool called po.com which
gives you access to uh all of these
different uh AI engines you know and and
you can look at which ones they're
giving you access
to to be able to use
these uh to to to
get outputs and things like that so I
love using po because it's a dashboard
that gives me access to Cloud 3 Opus um
gp4 um
mistol uh
Gemini the only thing that's missing is
you don't get grock because there's
no
um there's no version of grock this is
not the same grock grq it's a play on
words on that it's actually meta's llama
2 which llama 2 is yeah it's okay uh I'd
rather use mistol mistol large which is
pretty cool it's an open it's an open
source AI so anyways we have all these
AI engines you're like oh my gosh which
one should I use well here's the best
way that I say to figure that
out come up with a
prompt and ask it the same question how
can I Market a coaching
business or actually let's do
uh an online subscription membership
business if I don't have money to spend
on
ads okay and what you'll notice is just
this one question alone
is going to get answered very
differently across these different uh AI
models if I just go into them and I
start asking and I'm just going to click
through I'm just going to start asking
the same question of all these
various AI models to see which output it
gives me and the answers are going to be
different across all of them
okay there are several ways Leverage
social media of course content marketing
influencer marketing email marketing
referral partner optimize your website
free trial webinars leverage user
generated content you notice it does not
mention paid advertising on here very
much because a lot of these are
programmed to not mention paid
advertising a lot of what you're going
to find on the internet doesn't mention
paid
advertising there is a tool as well that
I like to use and and and again like I
said grock the real grock is only
available ailable on X uh which is the
platform that Elon
Musk has right here then there's fun
mode and then regular mode I prefer fun
mode and and so this is going to search
the X platform and give you
outputs content marketing social media
marketing email marketing these are
better these are in a better order I
think SEO guest posting PR
Partnerships
yeah
cool Monitor and analyze your results
pretty similar to what mistol came up
with interesting or
llama okay another one that's out there
is called
perplexity and
perplexity is very unique and that it's
different than every other engine
because it
will ask a question and then it will ask
you another question what's the Focus
Education
perfect and then it's going to find
sources over 30 sources from around the
web
various
resources SEO optimized of course so
obviously they're promoting SEO because
they're OBO optimized but the outputs
that it's going to give us are very
intelligent leverage free content
webinars and by the way if you want to
learn stuff perplexity is my go to for
learning things you can even add it to a
a collection right here right we can do
membership
sites uh you can add like a like a
little Emoji to it
and and um you know we could say how do
we Market an online
subscription develop a Content marketing
plan maximize social media marketing
again does not necessarily mention okay
point8 is now mentioning paid
advertising and so this is how like I
like to test certain AIS as I'm going to
see what is it actually mentioning is it
mentioning the stuff that I think is
going to be really valuable this one you
can have it search
videos now we found some videos here's
some videos from
YouTubers which is a great way to find
content that's why I love perplexity I
mean this video right here she breaks
down the pros and cons of various forms
of marketing without ads and things like
that how to Market your membership site
okay so you're going to find great
content and all of
that through that okay let's go back to
PO over
here let's see what um Gemini Google's
version says content marketing build a
community guest blogging those are
actually really good advice social media
marketing email marketing build an email
list right referral program
Partnerships low cost see it does
doesn't
necessarily talk about paid advertising
that
much most of these
don't which is very interesting that
you're not going to see paid advertising
mentioned in in a lot of
these Cloud 3 Opus content marketing
social media
marketing also does not mention paid
marketing paid
advertising GPT 4 blogging videos
podcasts
uh social media email marketing
networking referral incentive
SEO very few mention and it says it
might take you longer to see results
compared to paid ads oh you know you
know why some of yall like realize why
it's not saying paid ads on this and
this is where you're going to find the
limitations of learning from
me because sometimes the answer is right
in front of me my wife my wife laughs
she's like if it was a snake it would
have betch you I think it's hilarious I
asked it how can I mark it without paid
ads so
clearly it's answering me the way I
asked it the one that didn't actually is
perplexity so that's
funny explore paid advertising while
organic is great you could explore this
so it's pulling up a couple of Articles
as to why paid ads are valuable
it's an SEO article it's interesting so
it's about SEO but it's mentioning paid
ads subscription box blueprint ebook
that's cool she teaches how to do
subscription boxes 16 proven strategies
for subscription business webinars free
Plans free trials
freebies drip email retargeting
remarketing upsell partnership paid ads
Yep this is a great article by the way
whatever this site is member space Oh
yeah member space so they are a platform
that that does uh paid memberships and
they also seem to have really good
learning content you could connect
member space to a Squarespace site even
for example which is pretty
cool so
again
well there's another tool that you can
use oh they charge 5%
good decent pricing though so that's
cool okay so anyways AI allows us to do
research to learn stuff to do things
like that and then you can ask it like
additional questions okay if I was going
to just test out a $100 to $200 and paid
ads what
would the best process be to do this and
what I'm showing you right now is this
me as a coach and Mentor I coach and
Mentor people people all the time on how
to grow your business okay my business
is a seven figure business doing this
with people and the what what I do is I
actually show you how to do the research
yourself first off is one of the number
one things because I don't need you to
get all the information from
me so why I teach this stuff for free
and I give this away and then in my
coaching program if you if you become a
client of it
right and and we don't even enrollment
is isn't even open in my coaching
program right now if you go to my
website and click on coaching you can
find a waiting list to join my group
coaching
program and you can read about it you
can read about the different courses
that we offer and the different
trainings that we have available and
what we offer and how we help
people you know we even have a 30-day
money back guarantee I think we're going
to change this to a 10day here in the
future but as of right now
that's what it
is because information by itself isn't
that valuable it's your it's your
ability to implement and so what I can
give you is I actually give you all the
info for
free if you go check out my YouTube
channel if you go check
out my
podcast all this info is for
free it's all free it's all freely
available to you okay
we're hosting this live event March 11th
through the
13th and some of you that are watching
this right now you're already registered
for
that we're also going to be hosting this
one on paid advertising right here
okay but this one's called AI offer
Launchpad and many of you are registered
for this event right here oh look it's
looping me back around it's not going to
the page interesting I need to fix
that
and and I'm showing you in three days
how to build all this up I've been doing
this for two
decades uh the position your offer how
to simplify it how to automate it things
like that so if you're not registered
for this make sure to get registered for
the AI offer Launchpad and if you are
registered make sure to show up make
sure to attend all three days and as
well
consider grabbing the VIP upgrade the
event is totally free
but the VIP upgrade right
here
is it's 17 bucks until Monday till
Monday March
11th 17 bucks gives you access to three
days of the backstage pass with me to
ask me questions the recordings the
recordings of all the sessions you get
these pre-training you get my chat GPT
prompts for sales letters bundle getting
unstuck to take Massive Action Fun and
Freedom news trust for approach to
business and the VIP mindset training
all for
$17 as part of
just just joining us for this so I'm
excited to spend some time with you to
help you build out your marketing your
landing pages your sales copy your ads
all that even if you're not using paid
ads we'll show you how to use AI to help
you organically okay so I'm excited to
spend that time with you these AI tools
are amazing what I want to show you is
just one little PRP right here if I type
this in if you're going to use a small
test it can help you brainstorm ideas
and we're going to use all the we're
going to use all three of these various
AIS right here or not all three we're
using multiple AIS I'm going into all of
these different AIS and I'm asking it
the same question and this is how I do
research with
AI what is the goal generate leads cool
that's it perplexity asks the good
questions to effectively test out $100
to $200 of paid ads you need to Define
your target audience choose the right
platform right we use Facebook
ads conduct keyword research
yeah create compelling ad copy and
creative so again this output is based
off of what a lot of blogs are on the
internet and I can tell you this from
experience as somebody who's been doing
this a while a lot of this is really bad
advice simply
put I mean here might be a decent
article right
right search ads and for various
businesses this works well but if you're
in the coaching
industry I'm in the coaching industry
selling a membership give me some ideas
for $200 budget for this specific
industry 27 to
$200 a month
membership right let's ask get this
question as a
followup I'm not even going to read
through a lot of these cuz I know that
they're going to be giving me kind of
the same sort of crappy
advice
um Google is actually one of the best
and that's why I've been using Google a
lot but they're recommending you spend
the majority of your money on Google ads
of course they are because they're
biased let's see what so Facebook ads
right here they're recommending that you
do influencer marketing they're not
recommending uh Google ads cuz it's
Facebook's llama tool see these AIS you
you you can literally See Clearly if you
ask the right questions what their bias
is
even
okay and so yeah influencer Instagram
influencer marketing email marketing
content marketing decent
ideas for coaching do uh paid ads
Instagram ads LinkedIn ads and then
Google ads now it's you know know what
it's it's it's being honest with us
honestly I would eliminate Google ads
still from this
conversation uh mistol let's see what
mistol
says originally it said identify your
Target customer that's decent advice
Facebook and Instagram ads for webinars
downloadable guides LinkedIn ads Google
ads YouTube yeah again sponsored podcast
ads that's not
bad see what cloud 3 Opus says this is
like this is like the new kid on the
Block and everybody saying that it's
really smart at
reasoning Facebook ads make a lead
magnet related to your Niche design a
simple ad campaign daily budget of $5 to
$10 a day wow it sounds like I wrote
this I'm I'm I'm I have a lot of hopes
for cloud
3 this this brand new kit on the Block
that just popped
up literally couple days
ago Cloud 3
opus
and the advice that it's giving on this
question is
amazing I'm
impressed I'm absolutely impressed love
it gp4 looking to keep up
right find your unique selling
proposition Target the Right audience
choose the right platform create high
quality lead magnets so again gp4 is not
recommending Google ads why because it
actually is based on like legit data and
gp4 is still
Superior to all of these so you got
Cloud 3 Opus they're still mentioning
Google ads Gemini is also but gp4 is
willing to go outside the box and
actually not mention that and so again
if we look at this
gp4 gives us better advice better advice
it's
amazing you know what kind of advice is
grock giving it says grock social media
marketing Facebook Instagram LinkedIn
yep so again grock is not mentioning
Google ads that's why I trust it more in
some
things again a lead gen and boost
signups okay let's see what perplexity
says if perplexity mentions Google
ads it better not cuz anybody who
actually knows what they're doing in
this industry ah it mentioned Google ads
no why are you mentioning Google ads
it's just it's not good
advice but this is probably somebody who
makes money referring people to Google
ads Google AdWords at the top
see it's because a lot of these articles
so Google has ranked in their search
algorithm stuff that prioritizes this so
again I'll use perplexity for stuff but
my favorites are going to be grock
Cloud 3 gp4 and uh Gemini Gemini got
better it's not telling us to put our
whole budget towards Google ads it says
people might be searching for coaching
topics but to be honest a lot of times
they don't and you're going to and
you're going to they're going to they're
going to click on uh SEO optimized blog
posts which is very hard to get ranked
in this industry because there's so much
competition so I wouldn't even recommend
putting a lot of your effort towards
that you would do better
with Organic social media
content than this so like if I do this
watch this generate me a script for a
organic social
media content for Tik Tok or Instagram
reels that expresses the above info
right if I paste this into my favorites
my favorite algorithms right here see
these open source algorithms I'm not
necessarily getting the outputs that I'm
wanting a lot of them are are just not
the best
quality as far as that
goes but if I'm using some of my
favorites like
grock
and
uh here's
llama are you tired of being stuck in
your personal professional life need
guidance personalized coaching session
see that's so
Sil it's not like it's not reasoning
very
well
do you want to improve your whatever
without feeling overwhelmed or unsure
where to start so mistol is better I get
it it can be tough that's why I created
this
membership for just 272 so again you can
see the outputs aren't the best but
they're getting better Cloud 3 hey there
are you a coach looking to grow your
business and help get more clients see
the reasoning is much
better I've recently discovered a game
changing strategy on a tight budget
here's a deal with a budget of 100 to
200 bucks you can create targeted ads
imagine being able to reach thousands of
people don't take my word for it I've
seen coaches do this if you're ready
jump in give it a try check out my free
training I bet gp4 is probably going to
be better or Gemini I ever feel like
you're just one step away from Reaching
Your Potential in your business it's
where I come in to help you I help
people get massive leaps and with our
membership you get exclusive access to
me and a wealthy resources all for your
goals if you want a free strategy
session check them out don't take my
word for it so that's pretty decent
that's a decent
script right there for what I might say
but it's not doesn't have the depth that
I'm looking
for let's see Gemini hey everyone you
ready to unlock your full potential I
want to share with you exclusively in
Our member so these are like almost like
ads it's almost creating an ad for me
out of this and this is again some of
the limitations of these various
platforms grock hey there coaches you
ready to take your business next level
in this business I'm going to share with
you a powerful strategy that you can do
this the importance of having an aligned
audience did you know that if you have
an audience that loves your
content it can make a huge difference
organic is a great cost- effective way
to do this to show your expertise but
you got to understand your audience and
you have to show up consistently if you
show up consistently to share valuable
content you can reach the right people
the best way to do this find other
people that have similar interest to you
and collaborate with them and encourage
engagement host Q&A sessions pull people
ultimately organic social media can be
tough but you don't have to spend a
fortune on ads and if you're consistent
and share valuable content and actually
engage and get to know people you can
build your business and grow your
coaching Empire quickly and easily so
I'll tell you this grock gave me the
best outline for an organic piece of
content than any of those other
ones and that's why I continue to use
grock
that's why I continue to use this for
ideas it's it's it's intelligent it's
amazing so what I what I would do is I
would actually take grock's outline and
I would say can you
craft a video similar to this can you
please adjust the script to match the
following
instead so grock is now going to tell
all these other ones to come into
alignment with it and make some better
content we're going to go into all these
other ones and we're going to tell them
to come into alignment with what grock
says and this is a way that I like using
AI is to have one of them influence
another and then align them all around
what we're looking for
okay let's see
Gemini intro hey there amazing coaches
you ready to take your business to the
next level I want to show you how to get
more clients organically you have to
have an audience CU you know that having
an audience that's aligned with what
you're doing makes a huge difference
organic is cost effective you have to
know your audience you have to be
consistent collaborate with other it's
almost the same
thing it's not
unique it's not unique
either it's not unique cadell as
well let's see Opus are you ready to
take your coaching business Next Level
first off let's talk about the power of
organic growth do you know an aligned
audience who love your content can make
all the difference so this is actually a
decent
script Opus was able to to script it out
well for
us okay GPT 4 hey there you ready to
take your business level dig having an
aligned audience that loves your content
makes all the difference organic growth
cost
effective so again it wasn't outside of
the box and this right here is where it
gets fun this is the last thing I'm
going to show you brainstorm some
ideas to make
better reels based on the above idea one
specific idea and then script it out for
me to get maximum
engagement on Tik Tok
or Instagram reals or
YouTube we're going to paste this in
here and we're going to have it
brainstorm some ideas and this is one of
my favorite prompts is
asking the AI to brainstorm some
ideas one specific idea would be created
before and after
transformation are you ready to witness
an incredible transformation in this re
I want to show you how our coaching took
a client from zero in just 30 days got a
bunch of results this is so and so they
were here before they got started they
joined our program here's what happened
to them they were facing this challenge
they received this amazing
transformation
you should join our program you should
get on the waiting list that's pretty
good uh Gemini three proven strategies
listen as a business coach who helps
people uh in this I'm going to show you
three proven strategies to get more
clients first off you need to know your
Target customer inside out what are
their pain points what are their goals
once you understand them you can create
content that resonates you got to be
consistent though you got to keep
showing up and you got to share
something that's valuable actual
insights stop holding things back if you
want to attract more clients start by
implementing these strategies that's
decent cuz I asked it to
brainstorm know your audience because
it's so similar in mral and that one oh
this is good mistol is good here okay uh
organic hacks if you're struggling to
grow your business here's some organic
hacks number one share your story people
connect with people not just businesses
I like
this I like this and so as part of a
Content creation stack this could be a
great process right here
share your story connect with people use
engaging visuals collaborate with other
coaches so again I would bring this if I
was like teaching a
holistic piece of content right here I
would bring this one
together I would bring this one
together and what I like to do is I like
to paste them into a text document so
I'd bring I would bring these two
together from uh
Google and
mistol let's see what cloud 3 has do
this share success stories be consistent
relevant yeah so I don't like this one
actually that much GPT 4 Day in the Life
share a day in the life morning routine
very cool that's decent like that so
really our best brainstorming came from
grock mistel Gemini Cloud 3 got a little
it's not as good and and I can tell you
I know how good it is because I'm in I'm
I've been in this industry for so long
so I know what I'm
doing so so that's so interesting is
that those three gave us really great
ideas so now if I take all those ideas
combined and I go like this I say now
take the following and generate one
final script with the best ideas from
the
below so I did was I pasted all the best
ideas into one prompt and now I'm going
to bring them into all of these again
and this usually helps me script out
really great content and ideas as far as
this
goes by combining them together and
bringing all the different Minds
together these different Minds that the
that the that the AI
has okay hey there you ready to witness
a 30-day transformation Sam was
dedicated stpp in a rut joined our
coaching program here the experience it
wasn't all smoooth sailing here's what
happened okay Cloud
3 final script hey there you ready to
take your business Next Level first
thing is you need to know your audience
inside and out you have to be consistent
you have to share valuable content and
bonus tip share your story decent not
the
best let's see
mistl hey
everyone I help coaches here's somebody
that I helped here's all
decent it's not original though is the
thing transform your coaching business
with these top three growth
hacks share your story engaging visuals
collaborate with other coaches that that
one's also decent and then this one
Gemini
Pro know your audience be consistent
share valuable content use these visuals
and all
that
again
gp4
yeah so it keeps leaning into one two or
three of these
ideas let's see grock introduction know
your audience be consistent share
valuable content so again it's bringing
the strategy together and I agree with
all these pieces of advice but you
notice how they're all kind of giving
you the same thing now and that's really
where convergence comes in and that's
where um they're all kind of converging
on one
idea and so what I like to do is I like
to take a look at how can I help them
brainstorm even smarter and so what I'm
going to say is this if you were
designing an expert AI that is an expert
at the
above describe in detail what this AI
would do and then take on this role or
Persona in everything this person does
it should brainstorm unique original
ideas not regurgitate
its
inputs okay so this is where I'm
actually getting it to think outside of
the box to possibly design its own AI
function and then start to operate that
way and this is a more advanced strategy
with AI we're 33 minutes into this video
I'm giving you some far more advanced
strategies and ideas now
okay uh
mistl sleep
plan that's sleep plan because I was It
was a prompt I was using there let's go
back to
grock if you were designing an AI expert
what would it do AI expert in the
coaching business let's
see capabilities understand audience
content generation Persona here's what
it would
do perfect Gemini
llama natural language processing
wow that's crazy create a Dei a device
that converts your thoughts into fys
what the
heck see this is where stuff gets weird
with it it starts talking about stuff
that like I didn't even ask
it and it's like you should do this and
it's like oh those are the inside
information that they're that they're
talking about at
meta ask me anything session let's see
Cloud 3 deep understanding of the
industry data
driven
gp4
decent ah look at that so grock
sometimes I give it I ask it too hard of
questions and then it struggles to like
give me
answers so let's go into regular mode
and let's see if this works better than
fun
mode
it's
struggling sometimes I ask it questions
that it struggles
with so let me let me try to reframe
this um if you are designing an AI
expert based on the below describe what
they would
do
ideas
oh excuse me our allergies are terrible
here in Austin okay let's try a new
prompt let's start a new
chat it should be able to work
better the AI has been updated with the
new role please ask
questions
um bring storm ideas for reals and Tik
toks it's
interesting see if we can do that
let's just paste the same prompt in all
these as
well cool it's adopting the
role what to do what type of post to
make to brainstorm these ideas behind
the scenes give your followers a sneak
peek tutorials challenges collaboration
product review story time and so what
you notice is I've shown you how you can
use AI in 35 minutes to brainstorm a
bunch of ideas for your business and you
didn't even have to work with a coach or
anybody to tell you this or buy a
course PO is 20 bucks a month to get
access to
gives you all this Gro I think you got
to be part of x uh Premium Plus X
Premium Plus which is 16 bucks a month
so for 36 bucks a month you get access
to some
incredible
abilities let's see what cloud 3 says
this is this one will be
interesting uh content strategy develop
comprehensive strategy audience
engagement
Mistral
content creation social media strategy
find success stories see what llama says
llama should be decent because it's
trained on the algorithm of Facebook
create a day in the life challenge share
your personal story yeah this is
actually really good advice right here
from llama on this and you got to think
of what company released it as well what
are their motivations so Facebook is
always going to give you content
motivation with llama uh llama 2 you
don't know what llama 2 is it's an open
source algorithm them that meta AKA
Facebook
released so their goal in a lot of their
outputs is always what's going to
encourage the Facebook algorithm more
than anything
else Gemini Pro be more YouTube based
probably understanding creating YouTube
content like that perfect so these are
ideas you could create AI personas with
these uh you could use the GPT Builder
inside of chat GPT to do this create a
GPT that like does a lot of this stuff
for you so but anyways that's how I use
AI to brainstorm ideas that's how I use
AI to come up with ideas
and I might just take one idea from
prompting it like that pull it out and
now that becomes part of my marketing
plan as far as that goes and I'm using
these multiple AIS to give me various
ideas so hopefully this is helpful for
you I know this is a bit long uh but I
think this is a valuable lesson as far
as how to create organic content and how
to use AI to brainstorm ideas as far as
this goes all right again as part of our
training that we're hosting AI offer
Launchpad event that we're doing uh we'd
love to have you there would love to
have you join us we love to have you
join our our VIP on this as well you go
find the info at my website and if
you're watching this after the date I
guarantee you we have
another event coming up we do live
events for free all the time these are
live live and interactive I'm actually
on there with you they're not
pre-recorded
sessions I'm interacting with you live
helping you put all this together for
free in your business okay and then for
some people that they want to take it to
the next level we encourage join the
waiting list for the
accelerator you know we have over over
250 active members in here we've had
over 600 people coming through the
program in the last 2
years um and and it's it's amazing it's
an incredible resource the results that
we've generated for our clients are
amazing nine figures for
Sandy uh seven almost eight figures
profit we actually helped him do over a
million dollars a month seven figures
here with this
client again can't guarantee results the
FTC can come after me if I say that I'm
guaranteeing it but these are all
quantifiable these are all people that L
literally came to me and showed these
like they offered up this information we
didn't pull it out of them they they
gave us proof evidence all of this as
far as these go so
um I believe that if you are a mentor a
coach a trainer that's the best way to
grow your business is is going to be
webinars and and YouTube content and and
video content long form video content
like this even okay
and so if you are somebody who wants to
learn you want to grow you want to
discover what does it take to be
successful again can I guarantee that
you'll be successful by working with me
or even joining my coaching group or
going through one of our sessions no
it's impossible to guarantee that
because there's no way for me to force
you to take action to do the things that
that you say that you're going to do now
again if you're a coach if you're a
mentor if you've been good at coaching
and you understand persuasion you
understand that there are mechanisms
that you can use to motivate people to
take action I have intentionally removed
a lot of those from our system on
purpose where I don't pressure people to
take
action CU I I'm not codependent what I
require is I require I want to make sure
that it's a good fit for those that work
with me I don't ever want anybody to
feel pressured I don't want anybody to
feel forced into working with me and I
only want to work with people that I
think I can actually get results for and
if you need me to push you to get
results you're not a good fit to ever
work with me whatsoever you need to be a
selfstarter you need to be need to be
somebody who doesn't make excuses it
doesn't blame other people for why their
life isn't going how it wants and listen
I understand maybe you've been through a
lot maybe you had a bunch of crappy
stuff happen in your life I I've had a
bunch of crappy stuff happen in my life
too that I had enough to blame people
before but I also grew up with a silver
spoon essentially I'm a nepo
baby my mom is super uber
successful
multimillionaire coach Sandy Kowski
she's been doing this for 30
years she mentors people on the stock
market she has her book anomaly mindset
you can literally go find it anywhere
that books are
sold Amazon Auto you can get the hard
cover Barnes &
Nobles all of this
okay and so yeah I grew up
around really smart amazing
incredible
powerful people wh that page doesn't
work on her
site my mom what she does today is she
teaches you how to uh trade stocks
AI stocks it's one of the number one
things it's one of the biggest shifts
that's happening right now in the last
40 years she shows you how to get
in on some investments in these areas by
the way you
know the markets down right now if you
look
at you know there's there's stock in
corporations like Nvidia well those are
up jeez wow I remember it was right here
I should have got got in right there my
mom was telling everybody to get in
right there I
didn't it keeps going up because of AI
Microsoft keeps going up because of
AI Amazon all these because of
AI even the debt
Market Apple's getting hit a little bit
hard one that's getting hit really hard
right now is is
Tesla
but it's not getting hit hard as hard as
you know it
could so again my mom she teaches a lot
of this stuff various Industries things
like that you
know teaches you how to identify various
stocks I wouldn't say any of those
stocks I pulled up are good A lot of
them are very much in their highs it's
better to buy low instead of
high again I'm not a mentor in that
area um
my mom hosts live boot camps you know
this this coming week she's doing a live
boot
camp on how to trade
stocks 47
bucks right here she has her
membership 60 bucks a month right
here she got her VIP program right
here charges $2,000 a month for or you
can say big if you pay
annually so again this model for
business works if you work
it
and using AI to help you build out a lot
of your marketing I'll tell you this a
lot of the marketing landing pages and
offers and ads and stuff like that that
you see on my mom's
site AI was used to create a lot of
those
marketing okay and it's a lot of the
same proc process that I just showed you
for
brainstorming you can use it to
understand Investments things like that
again it's not perfect you got to learn
how to ask it the right questions but
it's valuable and it's amazing what it
can do so again always fact check things
use your head use your
brain don't worry about making huge
mistakes either you can do a lot of
incredible things with this stuff all
right
toxic